After three years I'm back at the Obscene and since it's raining and cold outside
let's head inside and have a look
Outro Music
I'm at the Tazza and Jane booth here and it's your first fashion raid.
Yes, I had my first appearance in Munich at the Avanta Dista show.
They did a fashion show there.
A fashion show, very exciting but this is the first time in a commercial environment.
How do you like it?
It's exciting. Very long days but a lot of very interesting people, very interested in what I'm doing.
And yeah, it's nice. Nice feedback.
Big visions alive, it's just a reflection, a world that never dies.
The image we create, and our image we design, it's a beautiful life, so when is the future?
Time moves so fast in a single direction
Fighting with the present, racing from the past
We're searching for something that can never satisfy
The reality of answers when lives are on the line
I waited a lifetime for the age of wonder a place that I remember in a
splinter of time a stranger in a strange life caught in the flow still searching
for answers among the neon lights it's a beautiful dream it's a beautiful life
it's just a reflection a world that must survive
Look what I found here. It's a catsuit I already own but this one has glitter on it so I wanna try it on.
So this is the PVC version and I just love the cut.
I'm already wearing Fernando boots so I want to try some other ones, something more colourful
You're cool now?
Yes, I have some colors.
Do you like racing bikes?
Do you like motorcycles?
Why not, yeah.
You gotta go fast.
never dies. The image
we create, in our
image we design,
it's a beautiful life.
So when is the future?
I'm here at one of my favorite designers, Schnittmuskel from Karlsruhe and I just asked
what's new and she showed me this belt
raspy
which is really cool to put on top of other things
Heaven has arrived, but don't let anybody know
You watered to my seeds, I think I felt something alive
Answered to my needs, and heaven knows it will be right
I'm here with Nicole.
Who are you?
I'm the maid of Maggi.
And what are you doing here?
I'm working since last year.
I'm working since last year for the McKee magazine and we hope you are all coming to
Pleasure Bay this year.
What's your job on the fair trade?
Making bubbles.